tgels.com 2013-04-18

# 10.12 Form: Web Site Privacy PolicyTransaxtions LLC ("Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of our customer's per sonal information. This statement applies with respect to the information that we collect from the Company Web site, located at www.tgels.com. Amendments to this statement will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance there of.I. INFORMATION COLLECTEDWe collect non-personally identifiable informa tion about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through your IP ad dress, computer settings or most-recently vis ited URL. We may also ask you to provide cer tain non-personally identifiable information about yourself, such as your age, household in come, buying preferences, etc. We do not col lect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us, by, for example, filling out a survey or registration form. The types of in formation that may be requested include your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.II. USE OF INFORMATIONIn general, we will only use the information you provide to us for the purpose for which such information was provided. We may also use this information to deliver to you information about our company and promotional material from

10.12 Form: Web Site Privacy Policy
Transaxtions LLC ("Company") is committed to
protecting the privacy of our customer's per-
sonal information. This statement applies with
respect to the information that we collect from
the Company Web site, located at www.tgels.com.
Amendments to this statement will be posted at
this URL and will be effective when posted.
Your continued use of this site following the
posting of any amendment, modification or
change shall constitute your acceptance there-
of.
I. INFORMATION COLLECTED
We collect non-personally identifiable informa-
tion about you in a number of ways, including
tracking your activities through your IP ad-
dress, computer settings or most-recently vis-
ited URL. We may also ask you to provide cer-
tain non-personally identifiable information
about yourself, such as your age, household in-
come, buying preferences, etc. We do not col-
lect any personally identifiable information
about you unless you voluntarily submit such
information to us, by, for example, filling out
a survey or registration form. The types of in-
formation that may be requested include your
name, address, e-mail address, and telephone
number.
II. USE OF INFORMATION
In general, we will only use the information
you provide to us for the purpose for which
such information was provided. We may also use
this information to deliver to you information
about our company and promotional material from
                       -1-

some of our partners, trend analysis, pattern
detection, and site administration. Your infor-
mation may also be used to contact you when
necessary and may be shared with other compa-
nies that may want to contact you with offers
consistent with your stated preferences. Users
may opt-out of receiving future mailings from
Company and other entities by following the in-
structions set forth in the opt-out section be-
low.
Non-personal demographic and profile data is
used to tailor your experience at our site,
showing you content we think you might be in-
terested in. This information may also be
shared with advertisers on an aggregate non-
personal basis.
III. USE OF IP ADDRESSES
We use your IP Address to help diagnose prob-
lems with our server, and to administer our Web
site.
IV. USE OF COOKIES
When you view our Web site we might store some
information on your computer. This information
will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar
file. Cookies are small pieces of information
stored on your hard drive, not on our site.
Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade
your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard
drive and steal information. Rather, they help
you navigate a Web site as easily as possible.
We use cookies to deliver content specific to
your interests and to prevent you from reenter-
ing all your registration data at each connec-
tion.
                       -2-

We use an outside advertisement server company
to display ads on our site. These ads may con-
tain cookies. The advertisement server company
may collect cookies received with outside ban-
ner ads. We do not have access to information
that would confirm the use of cookies by the
advertisement server company.
V. SECURITY
Our site has industry standard security mea-
sures in place to protect the loss, misuse and
alteration of the information under our con-
trol. While there is no such thing as "perfect
security" on the Internet, we will take all
reasonable steps to insure the safety of your
personal information.
VI. OTHER WEB SITES; LINKS
Our Web site contains links to other Web sites.
XYZ is not responsible for the privacy prac-
tices or the content of such Web sites.
VII. CORRECT; UPDATE
XYZ allows its users the option to change or
modify information previously provided. This
may be done through the following methods:
(1) e-mail the information to update@transax-
tions.com
(2) visit the Customer Service section of the
site and follow the
appropriate instructions.
Unfortunately, to the extent that such informa-
tion is also stored in other databases, we can-
not always ensure that such corrections or
                       -3-

deletions will reach the other databases. We
will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that
your information is removed from or corrected
in our records.
VIII. CHOICE; OPT OUT
You may opt-out of receiving communications
from our partners, and from us, by the follow-
ing means:
(1) send an e-mail to update@transaxtions.com
(2) visit the Customer Service section of the
site and follow
the appropriate instructions.
IX. PUBLIC FORUMS
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message
boards, and/or news groups available to its
users. Please remember that any information
that is disclosed in these areas becomes public
information and you should exercise caution
when deciding to disclose your personal infor-
mation.
Contacting us:
If you have any questions about this privacy
statement, the practices of this site, or your
dealings with this Web site, you can contact us
at privacy@transaxtions.com.
                       -4-
